https://theguyon41.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This notice discloses privacy practices for www.theguyon41.com and Fenceworks.info.
Tracking Technologies
We use technologies, such as cookies, scripts, pixels or other advertising tools to customize content and advertising on this site. This may be used for advertising, feedback on our content, trends, user movements on our site, analytics on demographics, etc to help improve our website and customer service.
We reserve the right to use tools such as cookies, pixels or other tools to allow social media sites to track visitors and target the interest of our users. We reserve the right to use these tools in compliance with the policies of social media sites such as Facebook, Instagram, or various other social media outlets.
Online Advertising
We employ third-party advertising and marketing companies to analyze use of our site, display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our partners use cookies or pixels to tailor advertising messages users see while visiting social media sites.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for content or privacy practices of such other sites.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
Questions or comments?
If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy, you can contact us at contact@theguyon41.com or write to:
Fenceworks
3177 MacArthur Blvd
Northbrook, IL 60602
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
